I'll show you the power of Abigail.
It's over.
Abigail is back, sealed away no longer.
The world is ending.
What happened?
What is that light?
It's so pretty.
Dante...
Lady! What are you doing here?
Looks like it's finally started.
What's started?
Alan Lowell?
There was once an alchemist by that name.
He was a human, but he was also a
sorcerer who employed various devils.
That was Alan Lowell?
Right.
Lowell...
There was just one devil that Alan
couldn't bend to his employment.
And that was Abigail, who was said to
have powers on par with the demon king's.
Using every bit of power he possessed,
Alan successfully sealed away Abigail's powers.
But seal them away was all he did.
He was unable to accomplish any more.
So to prevent Abigail's powers
from falling into anyone's hands,
Alan constructed many magical
barriers and spread them around.
Barriers so tight even a single
ant couldn't pass through.
Something came into being during the process
of making those barriers: the magic stone,
"Alan's Tear."
You know more about that than
anyone else, right, Nina Lowell?
I protected that magic stone according
to the ages-old tradition of our family.
That pendant, which could become
the key to unlock the seal on Abigail...
And all I could do was keep on running.
Why didn't you try to do
anything about the pendant
before you spent ten years on the run?
What was I supposed to do? Throw
away a pendant that summoned demons?
And yet, even if you destroyed the
stone, it would just break the seal.
Either way, it's all over.
The seal has been broken.
With Abigail's powers on his side,
no one could stop that devil anymore.
Because Alan Lowell is
no longer in this world.
Then what about Dante?
It's impossible. No matter
how strong he may be,
there's no way he could defy Abigail's power.
Watch out!
Hurry up and get away from here.
Shouldn't you get it in
gear and run away, too?
There's no point.
He won't be stopped now. No one can stop him!
Looks like he's shown himself.
What is that thing?!
Abigail.
The end of the world, eh?
Hey, hold it there, Patty!
Where do you think you're going?
Let me go! Let me go, Lady!
What do you mean to do?
Isn't it obvious? I'm
going to go fetch Dante!
That's crazy. You'll get yourself killed!
I don't care if I do!
--Patty!
--Wait.
I'll go too!
You...
Honestly! All he does is give me trouble.
I'll leave the rest to you!
Hey, what do you mean by that?!
It's worth placing a bet on.
The two descendants of Alan Lowell...
A miracle might happen.
Are you really the type
to believe in miracles?
Yeah...
Just this once, I'm starting to
want to believe in miracles, too.
Patty! Don't go charging on ahead of us!
It's no good, we can't get through this.
But if we don't get through here, we
can't get to the south wing's top floor...
All right, there has to be a
sprinkler control valve somewhere.
You wait here.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think something
this bad would happen; I...
Mom?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
Patty!
For making you lonely...
for such a long time...
Mom...
Well, this beats me. A little
cooler in here now, huh, you t...
How many of these small
fries do we have to fight?
My, are you tired already?
As if.
How nice for you. It looks
like this fry isn't quite so small.
Well, not small in body anyway.
Sheesh, when I think about how I'm
not gonna get paid for this, I could cry!
Why not send Dante a bill afterwards?
Sure, if he's alive.
Awfully quiet, isn't it?
So, what are we supposed to do?
I don't know either.
What do you mean you don't know?
Isn't there a rite or a spell or something?
Dante...
Patty!
Dante!
What was with those devils?
Patty... That pendant...
--Patty!
--Hey, wait, Patty!
What's happening? Where did Patty go?
The demon realm, I would think.
The demon realm?
But the pendant Patty has
contains a shard of Alan's Tear.
It doesn't have as much power as Alan's Tear,
but it's got enough
magic to at least protect her.
Dante...
Where are you, Dante?
This way?
Hey, there's just no end to these things!
Agreed. And it looks like
he's creating these minions, so...
So basically, if we don't rub
him out, this'll just keep going?
Probably.
Say, would you lend me a hand?
Pretty pathetic, huh?
So we've really just got
to rely on him, is that it?
Dante!
Dante! Dante!
Dante...
Dante!
Dante! Dante!
Dante, wake up! Run away!
Dante!
I'll take that out for you right now.
There's no way you'd die of a
little wound like this, right Dante?
Please, wake up! And then take
down the devil like you always do!
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
It's my fault, isn't it?
I'm sorry, Dante. Are you mad?
But I don't want this! I can't
stand to have this be our goodbye!
I... I haven't even said thank you yet!
It was so much fun getting
to be with you, but I haven't...
Dante!
Dante, please, open your eyes!
I won't get mad at you for
messing up your office anymore!
And I won't eat your strawberry
sundaes without asking, either!
Please!
Dante!
Dante...
There's no need to be afraid, little lady.
I just want to say a little "thank you."
After all, thanks to you, I was able
to get enough power to rule the world.
Hmph, you're no match for Dante.
When he comes he'll take you down for sure!
Dante's dead, girl.
There's no way Dante would
die at the hands of someone like--
Mom... Morrison...
Run, Patty...
Dante!
What?!
Is it... Is it really you, Dante?
Is there another man this
attractive out there?
Dante, that's...
Oh, this?
It looks like a certain
someone played a trick on me
while I was having myself a nice little nap.
Perfect timing.
The rest of the show is adults-only.
Patty, this is one time I
might owe you a "thank you."
You wait there.
As a reward, I'll give him a good
lashing from you after I deliver mine.
Anybody who pulls pranks like
this needs to be taught a lesson.
Morrison, I'll leave the rest to you.
Damn, you make me wait forever, and
then you go making selfish requests...
Sorry.
It looks like it's finally going to begin.
Jeez, Dante sure took his sweet time!
Heh, you've grown since I last saw you.
I'll pay you back for what
you did, make no mistake.
Can you?
After all, right now I have enough power
to rule even the human world,
let alone the demon one.
I've had just about enough
of your arrogant attitude.
In the end, child's play like
this is the most you can do.
Th-This can't be!
You can grow as big as you want,
and you can get yourself
world-dominating power...
...but it's pointless!
Hey, now!
Wh-Why? Why can't I win?!
I got power that was
top-class in the demon world!
I don't care how strong you are,
something is wrong with this picture!
Dammit, this is totally unfair!
Is it decided from the
moment we're born, then?!
That demons born without much power
are fated to be stamped out by you?!
I can't believe that!
If this is how things are, no
matter what I do, it's meaningless...
That's not it. It's about souls.
Huh?
Basically, someone like
you who's let his soul rot
can't measure up to someone with a
real soul just by getting some power.
Well then, strong, gentle
Lord Dante of the "real soul,"
you'll let me live even now, won't you?
Just like you have before.
No can do. You went too far.
But you know, I kinda liked you.
Y-You bastard!
Jackpot.
Dante!
Hey, now, go easy on me.
I'm injured, you know.
S-Sorry.
--Patty.
--Huh?
You'll always be with your mother
from now on. Have a happy life.
Hey, Morrison, drive me to the office.
Your car will still move, right?
You're such a slave-driver.
I'm injured too, here!
I see someone's in a bad mood.
Patty's departure really
did a number on you, huh?
What do you want?
Don't be stupid.
There's only one reason I'd come
all the way over to your office, right?
Then hurry up and tell me the deal.
No small talk, thanks.
Apparently a large number of devils
have showed up in a certain country.
It's a sweet job. The client's
filthy rich, so the pay will be good.
I hear little Patty's
doing well with her mom.
Sorry, but I'm on my way to a job.
I don't have time to hang out with you.
My, what a coincidence.
We're on our way to a job, too.
I imagine we're all going to the same place.
So in other words...
The pay for this job...
...goes to the fastest one, of course!
Fine, bring it on! Floor it, Morrison.
I knew it.
Really, that Dante trashes the
place right away if I'm not around!